Guide to the Dale R. Corson papers, 1963-1977
Corson, Dale R. papers, 1963-1977
- Series I. Administrative Papers
  - 1971-1972
    - Presidential Councillors., 1969-70 (Box 49, Folder 26)
      Newman, Floyd R.; Clark, Van Alan; Noyes, Nicholas H.; Olin, John M.; Donlon, Mary Todd, Walter L.
    - Presidential Councillors., 1970-71 (Box 49, Folder 27)
      Knight, John S.; Beebee, Alexander M.; Clark, Van Alan; McMaster, Donald.
    - University Hearing Board., 1969 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - University Hearing Board., 1969-70 (Box 49, Folder 29)
      Judiciary Committee.
    - University Judicial System., 1968-69 (Box 49, Folder 30)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Dickson, Larry; Scott, Alicia Onnami. Committee on Student Affairs.
    - General Judicial Affairs., 1969-70 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - General Judicial Affairs., 1970 (Box 49, Folder 32)
      Burak, David; Barlow, Mark; Hayter, David B.; Hawkins, Kenneth; Smalls, Frank; Bugliari, Joseph B.; Dickinson, Donald. Student Homophile League; Office of the Judicial Administrator.
    - Judicial Boards., 1969-71 (Box 49, Folder 33)
      Kisker, Harry E. Student members on judiciary boards.
    - Office of the Judicial Administrator., 1969 (Box 49, Folder 34)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Robertson, William R.; Bugliari, Joseph B.; Kennedy, W. Keith.
    - Office of the Judicial Administrator., 1969-70 (Box 49, Folder 35)
      Bugliari, Joseph B.; Rice, James C.
    - Office of the Judicial Administrator., 1970 (Box 49, Folder 36)
      Bugliari, Joseph B.; Solowey, Fred. Graduate Coordinating Council; April 8, 1970 Demonstration.
    - Office of the Judicial Administrator., 1970-71 (Box 49, Folder 37)
      Rovine, Arthur W.; Bugliari, Joseph B.; Plane, Robert A.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Kisker, Harry E.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman - Organization., 1969-71 (Box 49, Folder 38)
      Yaffe, Byron; Cook, Alice H.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman - Organization., 1971 (Box 49, Folder 39)
      Yaffe, Byron; Hart, Jocelyn; Cook, Alice H.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman., 1969 (Box 49, Folder 40)
      Cook, Alice H.; Muller, Steven. American Council on Education.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman. Cook, Alice H.; Sapakie, Alan L.; Telsey, Steven. Student records; Crisis Control Center; Information and Referral Service., 1969-70 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Office of the University Ombudsman. Cook, Alice H.; Barlow, Mark. Relations with black students., 1970 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - Office of the University Ombudsman. Cook, Alice H.; Whitlock, John H.; Sapakie, Alan L. Sex discrimination study; Minimum wage rate for student workers; Procedures for student-administration grievances; Rumor clinic., 1970-71 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - Office of the University Ombudsman., 1969-71 (Box 49, Folder 44)
      Cook, Alice H.; Shepherd, Dennis G.; Reinhardt, Patricia J.; Lawrence, Samuel A. Information and Referral Service; Rumor clinic.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman. Cook, Alice H.; Sapakie, Alan L., 1970-71 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - New York State Office of Ombudsman., 1969 (Box 49, Folder 46)
      Dunne, John R.
    - Safety Division., 1966-68 (Box 49, Folder 47)
      Barlow, Mark; Herson, James M. Firearm policy; Procedures for student demonstrations and confrontations; Police organization on other campuses.
    - Safety Division., 1968-69 (Box 49, Folder 48)
      Dymek, Eugene J.; Baker, Lance D.; Barlow, Mark; George, Lowell T. Students for a Democratic Society (SDS); Firearm policy.
    - Safety Division., 1969-70 (Box 49, Folder 49)
      Hall, Jackson O.; Mather, John. Campus security.
    - Safety Division., 1970 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      George, Lowell T.; Dean, William Tucker; Ruoff, Arthur L. Emergency procedures.
    - Safety Division., 1970 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      Africana Studies and Research Center, security; Bomb threat procedure.
    - Safety Division., 1970-71 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Coskey, Ralph. "Walk Without Fear" (film).
    - Safety Division Budgets., 1969-71 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      George, Lowell T.
    - Safety Division - Building Guards., 1970 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Safety Division - Building Guards., 1970-71 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Safety Division - Building Guards., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Safety Division - Building Guards., 1971-72 (Box 50, Folder S)
    - Campus Regulations, 22 Apr. 1969., 1969 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Safety Division Reorganization., 1967-70 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      George, Lowell T.; Peterson, Arthur H.
    - Collection of Firearms., 1969 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Cooperation with Law Enforcement Agencies., 1968 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      Thaler, Richard; Stamp, Neal R.
    - Safety Division - Applicants., 1967 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      Dymek, Eugene J.; Willers, Diedrich K.; Barlow, Mark.
    - Traffic and Parking., 1967-70 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      Durland, Lewis H. Administrative Board on Traffic Control.
    - Traffic and Parking., 1970-71 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      George, Lowell T.; Barlow, Mark. Administrative Board on Traffic Control.
    - Traffic and Parking., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 16-17)
      Hall, Jackson O.
    - Traffic and Parking., 1971-72 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      Richards, William H.; Hall, Jackson O. Traffic Bureau.
    - University Regulations for Maintenance of Public Order., 1969 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      Muller, Steven; Nettels, Curtis P.; Stamp, Neal R.
    - University Regulations for Maintenance of Public Order., 1969 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - University Regulations for Maintenance of Public Order., 1969 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      Fei, John; Stamp, Neal R.; Barlow, Mark; Moore, David G.
    - Office of the Treasurer., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 22)
      White, Karin; Newman, Floyd R. Cornell University Portfolio; Office of University Investments.
    - Office of the Treasurer., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 23)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Lawrence, Samuel A.; Boschen, Henry C. Functions of the University Treasurer; Black banks; Minority banks.
    - Office of the Treasurer., 1971-72 (Box 50, Folder 24)
      Durland, Lewis H.
    - Office of the Treasurer., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 25)
      Durland, Lewis H. Griffis Foundation; Church Project on U. S. Investment in Southern Africa; Project on Corporate Responsibility.
    - Wage- Price Freeze., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 26)
      Plane, Robert A. Association of American Colleges.
    - Wage-Price Freeze., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 27)
      Lawrence, Samuel A.; Willers, Diedrich K.
    - Office of the University Counsel., 1969-70 (Box 50, Folder 28)
      Cary, William L.; Goroff, Robert N.
    - Office of the University Counsel., 1970 (Box 50, Folder 29)
      Stamp, Neal R. "The Campus Crisis and the Role of the Board of Trustees" by Stamp.
    - Office of the University Counsel. Stamp, Neal R. New York State Dormitory Authority., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Office of the University Counsel., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 31)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Haus, Lance W.; Linowitz, Sol M.; Moiseichik, Peter.
    - Office of the University Counsel. Stamp, Neal R.; Seremetis, Stephanie., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Office of the University Counsel., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 33)
      Stamp, Neal R. Board of Trustees.
    - Office of the University Counsel., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Office of the University Counsel - Pennsylvania Higher Education Assistance Agency., 1970-71 (Box 50, Folder 35)
      Reeher, Kenneth R.; Stamp, Neal R.
    - International Technical Cooperation and Assistance Panel (ITCAP)., 1966 (Box 50, Folder 36-38)
    - United States Department of Commerce Technical Advisory Board., 1965 (Box 50, Folder 39-40)
    - Commission on Engineering Education., 1962 (Box 50, Folder 41)
      Hall, Newman A.; Everitt, William L.
    - Commission on Engineering Education., 1962-66 (Box 50, Folder 42)
    - Department of Defense Science Board., 1959-61 (Box 50, Folder 43)
      Brown, Harold; McKenzie, Lawson; York, Herbert F.; Shelton, Harvey W. C.
    - Office of Science and Technology., 1964-66 (Box 50, Folder 44)
      Rothberg, John C.; Hornig, Donald F.
    - Office of Science and Technology., 1966 (Box 50, Folder 45)
      Margolies, Daniel F. International Technical Cooperation and Assistance Panel (ITCAP).
    - Office of Science and Technology., 1966-67 (Box 50, Folder 46)
      Rothberg, John C. International Technical Cooperation and Assistance Panel (ITCAP).
    - Office of Science and Technology., 1967 (Box 50, Folder 47)
      Rothberg, John C.; Tallez, Theresa. International Technical Cooperation and Assistance Panel (ITCAP).
    - Office of Science and Technology., 1967 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Kreidler, Robert N. Science Advisory Committee; International Technical Cooperation and Assistance Panel (ITCAP); National Academy of Sciences.
    - Office of Science and Technology., 1967 (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
    - Office of Science and Technology., 1967-68 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      Hornig, Donald F. Science Advisory Committee.
    - National Science Foundation - Science Development Advisory Panel., 1964-65 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Smith D. D.; Harworth, Leland J.
    - National Science Foundation - Science Development Advisory Panel., 1965-66 (Box 51, Folder 6-7)
      Smith, D. D.; Haworth, Leland J.
    - National Science Foundation - Science Development Advisory Panel., 1966-67 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      Smith, D. D.; Haworth, Leland J. NSF University Science Development Program.
    - National Science Foundation - Science Development Advisory Panel., 1967-68 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      Smith, D. D.
    - National Science Foundation - Science Development Advisory Panel., 1968-69 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      Smith, D. D.; Bevan, William.
    - Office of the Provost., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      Plane, Robert A.; Kaser, David; Esman, Milton J.; Black, Max; Cook, Alice H.
    - Office of the Provost., 1971-72 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      Plane, Robert A.; Tobin, Thomas L.; Hillier, James; Kahn, Alfred E. Andrew Dickson White College (Proposed); Danforth Foundation.
    - Office of the Provost., 1970-72 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      Plane, Robert A.; Kennedy, W. Keith. Tenure policy.
    - Provost's Committees., 1971-72 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      Stamp, Maja; Reid, J. T.; Cook, Alice H. Pre-medical Advisory Committee; Affirmative action for women; Committee on the Status of Women; Committee on Women and the Arts.
    - Long-Range Planning., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 15)
      School of Hotel Administration; College of Arts and Sciences; Graduate School of Nutrition; New York State Veterinary College; New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing.
    - Long- Range Planning., 1971-72 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Office of Admissions., 1971-72 (Box 51, Folder 17)
      Snickenberger, Walter A.
    - Office of Admissions., 1972 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      Storandt, Robert W.; Snickenberger, Walter A.; Plane, Robert A.; Marcussen, W. M.; Scott, Robert A. College of Arts and Sciences.
    - Office of Admissions., 1972 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Computer Allocations., 1969-70 (Box 51, Folder 20)
      Plane, Robert A. Office of Computer Services.
    - Computer Allocations., 1970 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Computer Allocations., 1970-71 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Computer Allocations., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Computing Advisory Council., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Computing Advisory Council., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 25)
      Plane, Robert A.; Pottle, Chris; Dykes, Charles E. "Computing at Cornell - A Short History. "
    - Computing Advisory Council., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 26)
      Lawrence, Samuel A.; Humphreys, Alice K.; Dykes, Charles E.
    - Computing Advisory Council., 1971-72 (Box 51, Folder 27)
      Runner, Gordon H.
    - Office of Computer Services., 1970-72 (Box 51, Folder 28)
      Chauncey, Henry; Rudan, John W.; Chester, Geoffrey V.; Lawrence, Samuel A. Computers.
    - University Computing Board., 1970-71 (Box 51, Folder 29)
      Plane, Robert A.; Chester, Geoffrey V. Academic Computing Advisory Board.
    - University Computing Board., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 30)
      Rudan, John W.; Chester, Geoffrey V.; Plane, Robert A.
    - University Computing Board., 1971-72 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Division of Unclassified Students., 1965-71 (Box 51, Folder 32)
      Sampson, Martin W.; Gavin, John W.; Rideout, Blanchard L.
    - Female Studies Program., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 33)
      Farley, Jennie T. T. Russ, Joanna; Seremetis, Stephanie Kahn, Alfred E.; Gurowitz, William D. Hammes, Gordon G.; Plane, Robert A.
    - Female Studies Program., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 34)
      Bereaud, Jacques; Kahn, Alfred E.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 35)
      Whyte, William Foote; Kennedy, W. Keith; Carter, Lisle C.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 36)
      Reed, Theodore L.; Kahn, Alfred E.
    - McGill Consortium., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 37)
      Maas, James B.
    - McGill Consortium., 1971-72 (Box 51, Folder 38)
      Modular courses.
    - McGill Consortium., 1972 (Box 51, Folder 39)
      Cave, Gene C. B.; Oliver, Michael.
    - McGill Consortium., 1 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Minority Education., 1970 (Box 51, Folder 41)
      Jones, William D.; Jamieson, Janine. Native American Association; Ottinger Foundation.
    - Minority Education., 1970 (Box 51, Folder 42)
      Johnson, Houston; Toomajian, Charles R.; Knapp, David C.
    - Minority Education., 1970-71 (Box 51, Folder 43)
      Jones, William D.; Williams, L. Pearce. Williams' Plan for increasing fellowship support for minority graduate students; Tuskegee Institute; New York State Veterinary College.
    - Minority Education., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 44)
      Turner, James E.; Hunter, Delridge. Committee on Black Education; Office of Minority Programs; Office of Minority Affairs; COSEP.
    - Minority Education., 1971 (Box 51, Folder 45)
      Jones, William D.; Greenier, Ewart. Division of Educational Opportunity; Office of Minority Affairs.
    - Division of Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1970-72 (Box 51, Folder 46)
      Sampson, Martin W.; Plane, Robert A.; Brown, Stuart M. Campus Crusade for Christ International; Department of University Unions.
    - Continuing Education., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Brock, Stephen C.; Maas, James B.; Shew, Randall E.; McHugh, G. Michael. Alumni University; Center for Improvement of Undergraduate Education.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      Turner, James E. Ford Foundation; Black Economic Research Center; Urban Component of ASRC.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      Turner, James E.; Husa, Karel; Everett, Chestyn. United Black Artists of ASRC; To All Things Black and Beautiful; Rockefeller Foundation.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Turner, James E.; Plane, Robert A.; Murapa, Rudzuko; Kuusisto, Allan A.; Everett, Chestyn. Xerox Corporation.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center Book Account., 1970 (Box 52, Folder 5-7)
    - Africana Studies and Research Center Book Account., 1970-73 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Black Graduate Students Association., 1969-70 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      Hatchett, John; Jones, Philip M.
    - Black Graduate Students Association., 1970-71 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Osby, William J.; Leurgans, Paul J.; Cooke, W. Donald; Jones, Philip M.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Williams, L. Pearce.
    - Black Miscellaneous., 1970 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Jones, William D.; Edwards, William C.; Seligman, Martin E. P.
    - Black Miscellaneous., 1970 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Wilkins, Roy; Alien, Leon B.; Moynihan, Daniel Patrick. NAACP; African Scholarship Program of American Universities.
    - Black Miscellaneous., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Turner, James E.; Uzoaga, W. Okefie. Concerned Black Students; Atlanta University; NAACP.
    - Black Miscellaneous., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      Cooke, W. Donald; Whitlock, John H. Florida A & M University; United Black Artists of ASRC; COSEP.
    - CO8EP., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      Jones, William D.; Marcham, John; Carr, Carson. Latin-American students.
    - COSEP., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      COSEP Handbook.
    - COSEP., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      Turner, James E.; Mallory, Donald L.; Hunter, Delridge.
    - COSEP., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      Hunter, Delridge; Rubin, Gary L.; Dickason, Donald 6. Ombudsman's Report on COSEP; Cornell University Learning Skills Center; COSEP Handbook.
    - COSEP., 1972 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      Hurwitz, David L.; Lee, Gary A.
    - COSEP Committees., 1970 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      Purcell, Robert W.
    - COSEP Committees., 1970 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - COSEP Committees. Elliot, J. M.; Purcell, Robert W., 1970 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - COSEP Handbook., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 23)
      Hunter, Delridge; Plane, Robert A.; Kahn, Alfred E.
    - COSEP Handbook., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 24)
      Jones, William D.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Schultz, Andrew S.; Plane, Robert A.
    - COSEP Handbook., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 25)
      Rubin, Gary L.; Plane, Robert A. Cornell Daily Sun.
    - COSEP Handbook., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 26)
      Blumen, Isadore. Committee to Review the COSEP Handbook.
    - COSEP Workshop., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 27)
      Hirshfeld, Barbara B.; Bernstein, Alvin H.
    - Adviser to the Provost, Alain Seznec., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 28)
      Hirsch, Jacob; Schlesinger, Rudolph B.
    - Cornell University Press., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 29)
      Howley, Roger; Grossvogel, David I.
    - Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art., 1972 (Box 52, Folder 30)
      Johnson, Herbert F.; Solinger, David M.; Straight, Michael; Leavitt, Thomas W. American Association of Museums.
    - Andrew Dickson White Professors-at-large., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 31)
      Ashby, Eric; Paz, Octavio; Black, Max.
    - Society for the Humanities., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 32)
      Guerlac, Henry; White, Karen; Black, Max. Mediaeval Academy of America.
    - Center for Improvement of Undergraduate Education., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Office of the Vice Provost, Kennedy., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 34)
      Kennedy, W. Keith; Cooke, W. Donald; Steward, F. C. Isles of Shoals.
    - Office of the Vice Provost, Kennedy., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 35)
      Kennedy, W. Keith; Drake, Francis E.; Cook, Constance E.; Frank, Konstantine. Cohn Farm; Rochester Gas and Electric Company; New York State College of Agriculture (Kennedy's deanship).
    - Division of Biological Sciences., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 36)
      O'Brien, Richard D.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Morison, Robert S.; Steward, F. C. Committee on Field Biology.
    - Division of Biological Sciences., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 37)
      Wilkins, John W.; O'Brien, Richard D.; Morison, Robert S. Proposed transfer of the Division to the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences; Organization for Tropical Studies.
    - Division of Biological Sciences., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 38)
      Morison, Robert S.; Bronfenbrenner, Urie; Kennedy, W. Keith; Levin, Harry. Committee on Biology; Proposed transfer of the Division to the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.
    - Division of Biological Sciences., 1972 (Box 52, Folder 39)
      O'Brien, Richard D.; Steward, F. C.; Feeny, Paul P.; Feeny, Karen; Keeton, William T.; Gilbert, Perry W.; Kennedy, W. Keith. Affirmative action; Mote Marine Laboratory; Liddell Laboratory.
    - Environmental Studies., 1970-71 (Box 52, Folder 40)
      Long, Franklin A.; Palm, Charles E.; Dworsky, Leonard B.; Likens, Gene E.; Carter, Lisle C. Institute for Environmental Studies.
    - Environmental Studies., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 41)
      Dworsky, Leonard B.; Morison, Robert S.; Long, Franklin A. Program on Science, Technology and Society; Environmental Action Committee; Environmental Education Center (Proposed).
    - Environmental Studies., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 42)
      Comar, Cyril L.; Carter, Lisle C.; Brady, Nyle C.
    - Institute for Environmental Studies., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 43)
      Palm, Charles E.; Brady, Nyle C.
    - Laboratory of Ornithology., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 44)
      Sewall.
    - Mote Marine Laboratory., 1972 (Box 52, Folder 45)
    - Office of the Vice Provost, Risley., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 46)
      Risley, Robert F.; Bilson, Malcolm.
    - Affirmative Action., 1971 (Box 52, Folder 47)
      University of Rochester.
    - Affirmative Action., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 48)
      Cook, Constance E.; Williams, L. Pearce; Holmes, Peter E. Cornell University Affirmative Action Program; U. S. Office for Civil Rights.
    - Affirmative Action., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 49)
      Rivera, Ramon E.; Williams, L. Pearce.
    - Affirmative Action., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 50)
      Carr, Carson; Williams, Chester C. Yale University.
    - Affirmative Action., 1971-72 (Box 52, Folder 51)
      Parsons, Kermit C.; Rivera, Ramon E.
    - McKersie Paper on Affirmative Action., 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      McKersie, Robert B.
    - Affirmative Action and Campus Construction., 1971 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Tobin, Thomas L. Ithaca Building Trades Council.
    - Affirmative Action and Campus Construction., 1971 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Myers, Cleve; Dunston, James M. HIRE (Human Interest Regarding Employment); Ithaca-Cortland Builders Exchange Center.
    - Center for International Studies., 1971 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      Quester, George H.; Littauer, Raphael M.; Esman, Milton J.; Golay, Frank H. Peace Studies Program.
    - Center for International studies., 1971-72 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      Esman, Milton J.; Gair, James W. Ford Foundation; American Institute of Indian Studies.
    - Center for International Studies., 1972 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      Esman, Milton J.; Sola, Donald F.; Golay, Frank H. China Program; Northeast Consortium for Andean Studies; Undergraduate Interdisciplinary Program.
    - Center for Urban Development Research., 1971-72 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      Parsons, Kermit C.; Carter, Lisle C.; Isard, Walter; Jones, Barclay G.
    - Personnel Policy Planning Board., 1971-72 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      Willers, Diedrich K.; Yaffe, Byron. Cornell University Career, Summer Plans and Placement Center; U. S. National Labor Relations Board; Collective bargaining.
    - Collective Bargaining., 1969-70 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      Lumbard, Paul A.; Stamp, Neal R.
    - Collective Bargaining, Fordham University., 1971 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      Mortola, Edward J. Pace College.
    - Collective Bargaining, Fordham University., 1971 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      McConnell, John W.
    - Employment of Minorities., 1968-70 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      Hayter, David B.; Willers, Diedrich K.; Ross, Henry. Black Graduate Students Association; HIRE (Human Interest Regarding Employment).
    - Personnel Department, 1971-72 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      Willers, Diedrich K.; Baranowski, Alexander; Risley, Robert F.; Williams, Chester C.
    - Degree Programs for University Staff., 1969-70 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      Gold, Charlotte.
    - Degree Programs for University staff., 1971 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Fringe Benefits., 1971-72 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Personnel Policies., 1964-72 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      Corrigan, Elizabeth V.
    - ROTC., 1971 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      Bailey, Claude E.
    - ROTC., 1971-72 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      Chamberlain, Robert L.; Kahn, Alfred E.
    - ROTC Draft Proposal., 1970-71 (Box 53, Folder 20)
      Hittle, James D.
    - Report on ROTC by Robert J. Young., 1971 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Vice President for Research., 1970-71 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      Cooke, W. Donald; Vitro, Robert.
    - Vice President for Research., 1971-72 (Box 53, Folder 23)
      Cooke, W. Donald; Leurgans, Paul J.; Lierheimer, Alvin P. United States Steel Foundation; Florida A&M University; National Science Foundation.
    - Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory., 1971-72 (Box 53, Folder 24)